[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
She'll be fine.
I think you have to check on Tripp.
On how he's doing.
Where's Tripp? Bring me to him.
Come on, Alys.
Take me to Tripp!
Are you deaf or what?!
Alys!
What is that woman doing here?
You almost killed him!
You almost killed my son!
And you killed your own baby?!
What kind of mother are you?!
I always lose something whenever I choose you.
I hate you!
I don't want you in my life anymore.
Let's end this.
- Ma'am Kat? - Yes, Ma'am?
Where is the patient staying here?
Weren’t you informed, Ma’am?
About what?
He's gone.
Yes, Ma'am.
It happened recently.
Oh my God.
What happened? I thought he was recovering.
Sorry, Ma'am.
What I meant was good news.
He's gone because he was transferred.
Oh my God!
Ma'am Kat! You scared me!
Sorry.
Where was he transferred?
Which room?
He isn't here, Ma'am.
He's been moved to another hospital.
Which hospital?
Sorry, Ma'am. I honestly don't know.
- Please. - Faster!
I just need to know where Mr. Palma was transferred.
Ma'am,
I'm sorry. You're not family.
We cannot disclose any information to you.
So what if I'm not his immediate family?
I'm his friend.
Am I not allowed to be concerned?
What I'm asking you is simple,
tell me where he was moved!
Ma'am, please calm down.
You've got some nerve asking me to calm down!
I've been asking calmly the whole time. Haven't I?
It's useless to keep—
- Ma'am, calm down. - What the hell?
- Ma'am, calm down. - Don't fucking touch me!
Just tell me where they transferred him!
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
Again, we cannot release any information to you.
You can't take him away from me!
What is that woman doing here?!
I left with my son healthy!
And now I returned?
And now he's in a coma with multiple internal injuries?
You do not deserve to see my son!
But Tripp
I need to see you again.
I need to make it up to you.
My baby!
I'm so sorry.
Why?
Why did this have to happen to me?
To the people I love.
Am I cursed?
Do I deserve all of this?
Am I destined to be everyone's burden?
Maybe yes.
Maybe this is all on me.
I'm not just hurting myself.
But everyone else who loves me.
I don't deserve them,
because all I ever do is hurt them.
I don't deserve to be happy.
I tried to get up.
I tried to put everything right.
But the more I try to fix my mistakes,
the more I hurt people around me.
The more I lose them.
Until I don't know if I have anything left to fight for.
I give up.
I wish I could be numb to all of this.
I just want everything to stop.
To run away from this feeling.
I just want to rest.
You almost killed my son!
And you killed your own baby?!
What kind of mother are you?!
I don’t want to do this anymore.
I killed my baby.
I don't want to see,
or hear
or feel any of this.
I just want to let go of this weight.
All I want is my peace.
I want my peace.
Mommy, I need help.
I need help, Mommy.
I can't take this anymore.
Three months.
Three months in rehab.
I'm not sure if I'm completely okay.
Maybe yes.
Maybe no.
All I know is I am better.
But the guilt of losing people still haunts me.
Sometimes I still blame myself.
Sometimes I just want to run.
Leave.
But I don't know where and when.
Thank you for buying my pastry shop, Tofer.
It's nothing, Alys.
It’d be such a waste if your baby ended up with someone else.
I can't really imagine anyone running it but you.
I realized...
I needed a clean slate.
That place just held way too many memories for me.
And maybe it's time that I let it go.
Alys...
You know what?
This is the first time in a really long time,
that I've made a decision that's really for me.
Then, I'm so proud of you for that.
Thank you, Tofer.
Tofer?
Hmm?
I'm just curious.
Do you know where Tripp is?
Okay.
Would Kei know?
Hello, Kei?
Alys! I'm glad you're better.
I miss you.
I miss you too, Kei.
Why’d you call?
I just wanted to ask if you know
where Tripp is.
Alys...
No, I just wanted to know.
I'm sorry, Alys.
I don't know either.
Don't worry.
I’ll call you as soon as I find out anything.
No worries, Kei.
Thanks.
Who else can I ask?
Alys, maybe he’s still upset with you.
But how will you know if you won't try?
Oh, Alys.
You called?
Hello, Uncle.
How are you coping?
I'm okay.
Compared to 3 months ago.
Good for you.
Uncle...
Have you heard anything about Tripp?
Don't worry about him.
We're hoping he does well in the States.
States?
Uncle?
Alys, he's in California now.
California?
Yes, in a hospital there.
Anyway,
I need to go. I have a meeting.
Thank you, Uncle.
Thank you so much.
Alys?
Hope you are not blaming yourself.
It was an accident.
Okay?
Okay, Uncle.
California.
This is my sign.
I was looking for a where and a when.
I don't know where Tripp is but
now I know where to start.
For the longest time,
I thought my life stopped, the day my world fell apart.
Why aren't you answering me?
Where are you, Bestie?
I thought I'd carry the guilt forever.
Maybe this will always be a part of me.
Hello, Alys, please! Answer the phone!
But I won’t let it define my life.
I want to live differently now.
Alys.
Pick up!
Not to escape the past,
but to learn how to live with it.
I don't know what's waiting for me there.
But I'm ready to face it.
Okay, thank you.
Dane? Did you reach her yet?
Not yet. Her phone's turned off.
She won't even reply to any of my messages.
I asked all our relatives. They had no idea.
I even asked Aya.
We came by Alys' condo earlier.
And?
She's not there.
Her closet's emptied out.
So it means she left?
I mean, didn’t she say anything to anyone?
Or tell anyone where she's going?
Why would she leave without telling anyone?
Maybe, Drake?
God, I still hate him.
Ah, Drake!
- Oh, Drake! - Is Alys here?
She's not at her condo.
We've been looking for her too.
We were about to ask you that.
Alys...
Where did you go?
New country, new air.
No one knows me here.
I hope I find Tripp here.
But can I truly live on my own?
Without relying on anyone?
I can.
You can, Alys.
You can do this.
I have to do this.
So, you're applying as a waitress?
Do you have any experience?
Yes.
I used to run my own pastry shop.
Then why apply as a waitress?
I just wanna start simple.
Hello?
Yeah, yeah! Do you know where Alys is?
Please give us an update, okay?
Because I'm so worried about her.
Yeah, sorry to bother you.
But do you know where Alys is?
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Is there any chance
you've seen Alys there in New York?
Hello, Harper?
Yeah, have you seen Alys?
It's been three months.
Please update me, okay?
Alright, bye!
Good morning, Tommy.
Good morning, Alys.
Hello?
Mom!
Alys...
Where are you?
Everybody's worried about you.
I know.
I'm sorry I made you worry, Mom.
But please don't worry about me.
I'm okay.
Where are you, Alys?
California.
What?
What are you doing there?
I just —
I just need this, Mom.
Please trust me on this.
I need this for myself.
And Mom...
Can you keep this between the two of us for now?
And, I promise,
you don't have to worry about me.
I can handle myself. I'll be okay.
I'll call you. I'll always update you.
It's a promise.
Okay, I will not tell anyone.
But please Alys, please call me, okay?
Keep your promise!
I will.
I love you.
I love you so much, Alys.
Alys, I know you need space.
I know you need to cut me off from your life.
But not knowing where you are is driving me insane.
Dane!
Don't be overexcited. I'm still mad at you.
But even if I am mad at you.
I know you're going crazy not knowing where my sister went.
Has she called?
Yeah, she called mom.
And she doesn’t want mom to tell anyone.
Even Aya.
But of course,
Mom still told me.
Because she knows people are worried about her.
So, where is she?
California.
Don't you dare follow her.
Give her space, Drake.
Don't worry, Dane.
I won’t do anything that could put Alys in danger again.
I've learned my lesson.
Okay.
Hi, excuse me.
Oh, hi. How can I help you?
I'm looking for a patient.
His name is Tripp Marco Palma.
I was just wondering if he's admitted here.
Alright, hold on. Let me check him.
I'm looking for a patient named Tripp Marco Palma.
I am sorry, ma'am.
We don't have anyone under that name here.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I won't stop until I find you, Tripp.
Dear Alys,
I don't know if this email will ever reach you.
I don’t know if you’ll ever read this.
But I'll write you anyway.
Life's been...
quiet lately.
Morning, Tommy.
Morning, Alys.
Morning, Abby.
Good morning, Kev.
Morning, Alys.
I guess that's what happens when someone important
disappears from your life.
They said you left.
I don't know where exactly,
but I hope you're okay.
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am. How can I help you?
Is there a patient here named Tripp Marco Palma?
Okay, ma'am. Wait.
Hold on.
What if he's not here too?
How are you related to the patient?
I hope you find the peace you are looking for.
You don't need to reply.
I understand if you still don’t want to.
Just know that wherever you go,
I'm still here.
Waiting...
and I’ll continue to wait for you.
Finally, I found you, Tripp.
Hello, Marco.
You were so hard to find.
I had to go all the way here in California.
And you know me, I'm stubborn.
I'll always find you wherever you go.
So please, Tripp.
Wake up.
I’m never leaving again, I promise.
I won't leave until you wake up.
I’m so sorry.
Three years have passed,
and this is my life now.
Still working as a waitress in this small cafe.
And in this country, I am a nobody.
Thank you for coming. See us again!
Hey, I got this.
- You sure? - Yeah, for sure.
Please take a break.
Thanks. See you in fifteen.
Okay, sounds good.
But surprisingly, it feels good.
No pressure, no stress.
705 emails.
That madman hasn't stopped.
Hi, Alys.
How are you?
We're doing fine here.
Your Mom and the others are doing well.
And Dane, he's still angry with me.
But that's okay.
Anyway, I made a tiny altar in memory of Marco.
Why did you name him Marco?
Tripp's still alive, isn't he?
But fine.
I won't question it.
Because you're Marco's mother.
3 years, 765 emails.
Zero reply.
They told me, “Give up, Drake.”
She's moved on.
But hell, I won't.
You haven't forgotten about me, right?
You said you love me.
You just need a break.
I wish you were here.
I love you.
I still do.
And I will always.
You said you love me.
I'm holding you to that, Alys.
Hi, Abby.
Hi, Alys.
Hi, Kevz.
- Hi, Tommy. - Hi, Alys.
Hello, you.
I'd rather die than replace you in my life.
You can call me a fool, Alys.
If you ever find someone new,
don't invite me to your wedding, okay?
Or don't marry at all.
You're still married, remember?
I love you, Alys.
Always.
Drake.
Hi, my name is Alys.
What can I get for you today?
- Go ahead, Tommy. - Okay.
Bye, Alys.
Are you okay, Alys?
What?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just got distracted.
Okay.
Hey, Tommy.
Don't you have a date tonight?
Yeah.
Well, go on.
I'll close the shop for you.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Don't you need to visit your friend at the hospital?
I will, but after this.
I'm not in a rush anyway, so just go ahead.
Okay. Thank you so much.
You're the best.
- You owe me one. - Okay.
I love you, Alys.
Always.
Drake.
I'm not mad.
I just needed space to rebuild my life.
I'm done loving someone too much.
When you love someone too much,
you leave nothing for yourself.
What if they leave you?
Then you lose everything.
And I promised Tripp.
I'm not going home until he wakes up.
Hello, Silly.
Can you give me a smile?
I had a boring day at work.
Nothing really happened.
Wake up, please?
You know, I've gotten really good at making coffee.
I'll make you some.
You won't be able to drink it, though.
Smell it instead.
Hello, Marco.
I’m sorry.
I can only visit twice a month now.
I’m working two shifts now.
Anyway, are you ready?
Once upon a time, there was a man who used
to love chasing sunsets.
He searched far and wide for the most beautiful sunset but
he couldn't seem to find it.
[singing] Happy birthday to you.
[singing] Happy birthday, happy birthday.
I wish...
you'd wake up already.
I'll be back next week, okay?
I love you, Marco.
Where’s Tripp?
Excuse me.
Are you looking for Mr. Palma?
Yes.
Did his mother transfer him to a different hospital again?
She always does that.
His mom picked him up.
Oh my God.
Where have you gone now, Tripp Marco Palma?
Excuse me, ma'am.
No, he was discharged two weeks ago.
Discharged?
Yes, he's been responsive for a few months now.
He could hear, he could feel.
We were surprised that he finally woke up now.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Tripp.
[singing] Happy birthday to you.
[singing] Happy birthday, happy birthday.
I wish...
you'd wake up already.
I'll be back next week, okay?
I love you, Marco.
I know a place where you can get Adobo.
On the last episode of Dating Alys Perez.
Hi, sir. How may I help you?
Zy!
You did nothing wrong.
I have never blamed you.
I am not blaming you.
I will never blame you.
I'm coming home to you.
Turn around.